arwscripts.com 2017-06-18

# ARWScripts - Privacy Policy

ARWScripts respects your right to privacy. We asure you that all information submitted to us during the process of using our sites and services will be kept strictly confidential and used solely by ARWScripts for marketing purposes and to improve the user experience. At ARWScripts we do not share, sell, rent, or distribute to any third party outside of ARWScripts with the exception to legal purposes, regulation, or governmental authority. 

### Information Collected

The information collected by ARWScripts is only what is provided by users of ARWScripts websites. These include name, email addresses, and mailing addresses, and any additional information submitted by voluntarily by users for the purposes of customer support. ARWScripts also collects non-personally identifiable information from users accesssing any ARWScripts site. These include user IP addresses, internet providers, operating system, internet host, referral URL's, number of visits, pages visited and the amount of time spent on ARWScripts sites. ARWScripts does not collect and store any information such as credit card details. 

### How The Information Collected Is Used

We mainly use the information collected to provide a service which has been requested by ARWScripts users such as of sales and customer support. ARWScripts may also use the provided email addresses to contact users periodically to inform them of ARWScripts service and site announcements such as new products, promotions, and site or service updates. You may choose at any point to unsubscribe to these emails. ARWScripts may also use the email addresses at any point to contact you for customer support services. ARWScripts withholds the right to use any of the information provided by users for the purposes improving our site user experience, improving our advertising and marketing, and for legal disputes if required. 

### Linked Sites

At any point we may provide ARWScripts users with links to websites operated by other parties. These links are provided because they may be of use to users for any particular reason. ARWScripts terms and conditions as well as privacy policy does not extend to third party sites and we are not responsible for the terms and privacy policy set by third party sites.

ARWScripts reserves the right to edit the above privacy policy at any time. Any changes made to the above privacy policy are active as soon as they are updated. Users of ARWScripts sites agrees to regularly review this privacy policy and be aware of any alterations made to them. By the continual use of ARWScripts sites and services, users agree to the above.
